http://www.backschoolofatlanta.com/site-usage/terms-of-use

Terms of Use
Last updated: January 27, 2017Please read these Terms and Conditions (“Terms, Terms and Conditions”) carefully before using the www.thebackschool.net website (the “Service”) operated by The Back School (“us”, “we”, or “our”).Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned upon your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who wish to access or use the Service.By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you do not have permission to access the Service.DISCLOSURENeither the Director nor any of the instructors of The Back School has any personal, financial or material interest in any of the ergonomics products, books or printed materials, or other reference materials including websites mentioned, discussed or referred to in any of our courses.COMMUNICATIONSBy creating an Account on our service, you agree to subscribe to newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information we may send. However, you may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.PURCHASESIf you wish to purchase any product or service made available through the Service (“Purchase”), you may be asked to supply certain information relevant to your Purchase including, without limitation, your credit card number, the expiration date of your credit card, your billing address, and your shipping information.You represent and warrant that: (i) you have the legal right to use any credit card(s) or other payment method(s) in connection with any Purchase; and that (ii) the information you supply to us is true, correct and complete.The service may employ the use of third party services for the purpose of facilitating payment and the completion of Purchases. By submitting your information, you grant us the right to provide the information to these third parties subject to our Privacy Policy.We reserve the right to refuse or cancel your order at any time for reasons including but not limited to: product or service availability, errors in the description or price of the product or service, error in your order or other reasons.We reserve the right to refuse or cancel your order if fraud or an unauthorized or illegal transaction is suspected.AVAILABILITY, ERRORS AND INNACCURACIESWe are constantly updating product and service offerings on the Service. We may experience delays in updating information on the Service and in our advertising on other web sites. The information found on the Service may contain errors or inaccuracies and may not be complete or current. Products or services may be mispriced, described inaccurately, or unavailable on the Service and we cannot guarantee the accuracy or completeness of any information found on the Service.We therefore reserve the right to change or update information and to correct errors, inaccuracies, or omissions at any time without prior notice.CONTENTContent found on or through this Service are the property of The Back School or used with permission. You may not distribute, modify, transmit, reuse, download, repost, copy, or use said Content, whether in whole or in part, for commercial purposes or for personal gain, without express advance written permission from us.ACCOUNTSWhen you create an account with us, you guarantee that you are above the age of 18, and that the information you provide us is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Inaccurate, incomplete, or obsolete information may result in the immediate termination of your account on the Service.You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password, including but not limited to the restriction of access to your computer and/or account. You agree to accept responsibility for any and all activities or actions that occur under your account and/or password, whether your password is with our Service or a third-party service. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.We reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in our sole discretion.INTELLECTUAL PROPERTYThe Service and its original content (excluding Content provided by users), features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of The Back School and its licensors. The Service is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the United States and foreign countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of The Back School.LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITESOur Service may contain links to third party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by The Back School.The Back School has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. We do not warrant the offerings of any of these entities/individuals or their websites.You acknowledge and agree that The Back School shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such third party web sites or services.We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third party web sites or services that you visit.INDEMNIFICATIONYou agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless The Back School and its licensee and licensors, and their employees, contractors, agents, officers and directors, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney's fees), resulting from or arising out of a) your use and access of the Service, by you or any person using your account and password; b) a breach of these Terms, or c) Content posted on the Service.LIMITATION OF LIABILITYIn no event shall The Back School, nor its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of or inability to access or use the Service; (ii) any conduct or content of any third party on the Service; (iii) any content obtained from the Service; and (iv) unauthorized access, use or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other legal theory, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.DISCLAIMERYour use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an “AS IS” and “AS AVAILABLE” basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance.The Back School its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Service will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Service will meet your requirements.EXCLUSIONSSome jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, so the limitations above may not apply to you.GOVERNING LAWThese Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Georgia, United States, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have had between us regarding the Service.CHANGESWe reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.By continuing to access or use our Service after any revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, you are no longer authorized to use the Service.CONTACT USIf you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Keep in touch
(800) 783-7536
Email Us
Subscribe to the Ergo Newsletter
Follow the Ergo Blog
BSOA is registered in the
government database in the
Central Contractor Registration
DUNS #088942396
BCSP COC Guide
Board of Certified Safety Professionals
Our courses may qualify for BCSP
COC points. See guide for details.
BSOA is approved by AOTA to
offer AOTA CEUs/Contact Hours.
Sign in
Email Address
Password
Forgot your password?
Create an Account
Take advantage of the features and benefits that make shopping and registering for courses faster and easier.
Register
Privacy Policy
<p><u>Last updated: July 24, 2018</u></p><p>The Back School (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the www.thebackschool.net website (the “Service”). Our office is located at 1962 <span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="Northside" data-wsc-lang="en_US">Northside</span> Drive, Atlanta, GA 30318.</p><p>This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.</p><p>We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.</p><p>We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at www.thebackschool.net.</p><h3>INFORMATION COLLECTION,&nbsp;USE AND STORAGE</h3><p>While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address, other information (“Personal Information”).<br><br>We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services. This information is stored in our database indefinitely so that you may access your Account Information, Order History,&nbsp;Online Courses,&nbsp;Webinars and <span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="Ebooks" data-wsc-lang="en_US">Ebooks</span>&nbsp;(as well as other&nbsp;pertinent&nbsp;documents and information related to our Service&nbsp;and Products).</p><h3>CHANGING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION<br></h3><p>You may login and change/update Personal Information stored in&nbsp;<span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="&quot;" data-grammar-rule="EN_QUOTES">"</span>My Account<span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="&quot;" data-grammar-rule="EN_QUOTES">"</span>&nbsp;/<span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="&quot;" data-grammar-rule="EN_QUOTES">"</span>Profile<span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="&quot;" data-grammar-rule="EN_QUOTES">"</span>.</p><h3>DELETION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION</h3><p>If you want us to permanently delete your Account/Personal&nbsp;Information from our database (note that it cannot be restored once deleted), please submit your request in <a data-cke-saved-href="/about-us/contact-us" target="_blank" href="/about-us/contact-us">writing</a>.</p><h3>LOG DATA</h3><p>We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.</p><p>In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.</p><h3>COOKIES</h3><p>Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a <span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="web site" data-grammar-rule="WEB_SITE">web site</span> and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.</p><p>You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help <span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="feature" data-grammar-rule="MASS_AGREEMENT">feature</span> on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.<br><br>If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.</p><h3><span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="BEHAVIORIAL" data-wsc-lang="en_US">BEHAVIORIAL</span> <span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="REMARKETING" data-wsc-lang="en_US">REMARKETING</span></h3><p>The Back School uses <span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="remarketing" data-wsc-lang="en_US">remarketing</span> services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.</p><h3>GOOGLE</h3><p>Google AdWords <span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="remarketing" data-wsc-lang="en_US">remarketing</span> service is provided by Google Inc.</p><p>You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <a data-cke-saved-href="http://www.google.com/settings/ads" target="_blank" href="http://www.google.com/settings/ads">http://www.google.com/settings/ads</a></p><p>Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on &nbsp;- <a data-cke-saved-href="https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout" target="_blank" href="https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout">https://tools.google.com/<span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="dlpage" data-wsc-lang="en_US">dlpage</span>/<span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="gaoptout" data-wsc-lang="en_US">gaoptout</span></a> - for your web browser. Google Analytics&nbsp;Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.</p><p>For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy &amp;&nbsp;Terms web page: <a data-cke-saved-href="http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/" target="_blank" href="http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/">http://www.google.com/<span class="scayt-misspell-word" data-scayt-word="intl" data-wsc-lang="en_US">intl</span>/en/policies/privacy/</a></p><h3>DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE</h3><p>We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.</p><p>You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.</p><h3>SERVICE PROVIDERS</h3><p>We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</p><p>These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.</p><h3>COMMUNICATIONS</h3><p>We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.</p><h3>COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS</h3><p>We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.</p><h3>SECURITY</h3><p>The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.</p><p>However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.</p><h3>INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER</h3><p>Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.</p><p>If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there.</p><p>Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.</p><h3>LINKS TO OTHER SITES</h3><p>Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.</p><p>We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.</p><h3>CHILDREN'S PRIVACY</h3><p>Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).</p><p>We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from <span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="a children" data-grammar-rule="A_PLURAL">a children</span> <span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="under age" data-grammar-rule="EN_COMPOUNDS">under age</span> 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.</p><h3>CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY</h3><p>This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 30, <span class="gramm-problem" data-wsc-lang="en_US" data-grayt-phrase="2017" data-grammar-rule="MISSING_COMMA_AFTER_YEAR">2017</span> and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.</p><p>We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.</p><p>If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.</p><h3>CONTACT US</h3><p>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please <a data-cke-saved-href="/about-us/contact-us" target="_blank" href="/about-us/contact-us">contact us</a>.&nbsp;</p>
Back to register
